themaverickspirit.com 2019-06-29

# Privacy Policy - TheMaverickSpirit

Your privacy is very crucial to us. This Privacy Policy dictates our data collection, processing, and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding the use, access, and correction of your personal information.

If you do not agree with the data practices defined in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Website or the Subscription Services.

Following are the outlines on how TMS deals with privacy –

### Information Collected On TMS –

  * We don’t collect any personal information about visitors without their prior knowledge.
  * Information provided by visitors include – name, email addresses (at the time of newsletter subscription or at the time of contact via contact form.)
  * Internet servers, Google Adsense, may automatically store your IP addresses.

TheMaverickSpirit acknowledges that you have the right to access your Personal Information. Our website users are responsible for correcting, deleting or updating the information they have provided at the time of opting the Subscription Service.

You can unsubscribe from our email marketing campaigns by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of your emails, or by contacting us directly.

### Information Collected On TMS Will Be Used To –

  * Share latest happenings on the website.
  * Improve our website based on feedback from our visitors.
  * Improve your stay @TMS by solving your requests and queries effectively.

### Is Data @TMS Unveil To Any Outside Third Parties?

No personal information of user will ever be sold out or shared with any 3rd parties. Any personal information will only be released in compliance with the law.

We can offer or include third party products/services which have separate/individual privacy policies. Therefore, we should not be responsible for any activities of these sites or third party links.

### Cookies –

TMS does use cookies to store information in order to track visitors preferences. Doing so helps us to send information according to visitor’s interest by tracking the pages he visits on TMS.

On the other hand, in order to serve ads on TMS Google as the third party uses DART cookie. Visitors may opt out the use of DART cookie by visiting the privacy policy of **[Google ad and content network](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).**

Apart from this if you wish to disable cookies, you can do so by following your respective browser options.

### Opt-Out Policy – 

Visitors/subscribers can easily –

  * Opt-out for further contacting upon request.
  * Update their personal information shared with us upon request.

### Subject To Change Privacy Policy –

Any changes made prior to the privacy policy will be updated here. If the changes are significant we will notify it via email notification.

Last Modified On – **23 May, 2018.**

### Drop Us A Line – 

Still have doubt regarding the privacy policy or how we maintain your personal information?

Drop us an email at – **admin[at]** **themaverickspirit[dot]com** and we’ll look further to sort it out.
